A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Administration, Program and Policy, RG 3 FA112
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, Program and Policy, 1
  - International Health Division, 1902-1973; 908; 27 document cases
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-35, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 137)
      Pro-35: Victor G. Heiser; Memorandum On the Present Status of the Work in the East; September 12, 1934
    - Program and Policy - Amoebic Dysentery, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 138)
    - Program and Policy - Animals Experimental Laboratory - Report - Pro Ani-1, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 139)
      Pro Ani-1: Supplementary Studies, Animals, Experimental Laboratory, Extract from Review of Program Presented to Scientific Directors (complete Statement filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review, March-October 1950 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review, March-October 1950 (Box 13, Folder 141)
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review, November 1950-December 1951 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review, November 1950-December 1951 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review, November 1950-December 1951 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review - Reports - Pro CR-1 - Pro CR-4, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 145)
      Pro CR-1: Alan Gregg; The Rockefeller Foundation Commission on Review of the International Health Division, Memorandum on International Health Division Program; October 27, 1950
      Pro CR-2: Warren Weaver; Relationship of the Mexican Agricultural Program to the Regular Program of the Division of Natural Sciences in Latin America; July 5, 1950
      Pro CR-3: The Rockefeller Commission on Review of the International Health Division, Public Health Education; 1950
      Pro CR-4: Dr. John C. Bugher; The Rockefeller Foundation Commission on Review of the International Health Division Laboratories in New York; September 1950
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review - Reports - Pro CR-5a, 5b, 6, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 146)
      Pro CR-5a: The Rockefeller Commission on Review of the International Health Division, Suggestions from Staff of International Health Division Regarding Program; 1950
      Pro CR-5b: The Rockefeller Commission on Review of the International Health Division, Additional Suggestions Regarding Program from International Health Division Staff; 1950
      Pro CR-6: Alan Gregg; The Rockefeller Commission on Review of the International Health Division, Memorandum on International Health Division Program; October 27, 1950
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review - Reports - Pro CR-7 - Pro CR-9, 9a, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 147)
      Pro CR-7: The Rockefeller Commission on Review of the International Health Division, Other Organizations Which Have International Health Programs or Related Activities; December 1950'
      Pro CR-8: Dr. A. W. Warren; The Rockefeller Commission on Review of the International Health Division, A Review of the International Health Division Program on Yellow Fever; 1950
      Pro CR-9: Report of the Rockefeller Foundation Commission on Review of the International Health Division (copy filed RG 3.1 920 Pro-1); November 1951
      Pro CR-9a: Meeting of the Rockefeller Commission on Review of the International Health Division; May 19, 1950
    - Program and Policy - Commission on Review - Staff Suggestions - A-Z, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Program and Policy - County Health Work, 1912-1939 (Box 14, Folder 149)
    - Program and Policy - Diphtheria - Report - Pro Dip-1, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 150)
      Pro Dip-1: Diphtheria, Extract from Review of Program Presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Health Services, 1916-1940 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - Program and Policy - Health Services - Reports - Pro HS-1, 2, 1942, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 152)
      Pro HS-1: Extract from Review of Program Presented to Scientific Directors; September 11, 1942
      Pro HS-2: Aid to State and Local Health Services; November 1951
    - Program and Policy - Hepatitis, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - Program and Policy - Hookworm, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 154)
    - Program and Policy - Hookworm - Reports - Pro Hook-1 - Pro Hook-2, 1913, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 155)
      Pro Hook-1: Hookworm, Extract from Review of Program Presented to Scientific Directors (complete Report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
      Pro Hook-2 DR-7: The Rockefeller Health Commission, Outline of Plan of Work for the Eradication of Uncinariasis in Foreign Countries; June 18, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Malaria, 1913-1959 (Box 15, Folder 156)
    - Program and Policy - Malaria, 1913-1959 (Box 15, Folder 157)
    - Program and Policy - Malaria - Report - Pro Mal-1, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 158)
      Pro Mal-1: Malaria Conference; October 1935
    - Program and Policy - Malaria - Report - Pro Mal-1b - Pro Mal-4, 1942-1955 (Box 15, Folder 159)
      Pro Mal-1b: Malaria; September 1, 1942
      Pro Mal-2: Dr. Paul F. Russell; World-Wide Activities of the Rockefeller Foundation in the Development of Malaria Control (prepared for Raymond B. Fosdick in connection with the history of the Rockefeller Foundation); 1915-1949
      Pro Mal-3: 50 Anos da Fundacao do Instituto de Malariologia e Sua Projeccao No Futuro
      Pro Mal-4: Dr. Paul F. Russell; Memorandum, The Influence of the Rockefeller Foundation on Modern Malariology; March 8, 1957
    - Program and Policy - Mental Hygiene, 1932-1942 (Box 15, Folder 160)
    - Program and Policy - Mental Hygiene, 1932-1942 (Box 15, Folder 161)
    - Program and Policy - Mental Hygiene - Report - Pro Men-1, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 162)
      Pro Men-1: Mental Hygiene, Extract from Review of Program Presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Nursing, Public Health, 1922-1950 (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - Program and Policy - Nursing, Public Health, 1922-1950 (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Program and Policy - Nursing, Public Health - Reports - Pro N, Ph-1 - Pro N, Ph-3, 1934-1937 (Box 15, Folder 165)
      Pro N, Ph-1: Mary Beard; Five Year Plan, Nursing, International Health Division (copy filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-22a); April 20, 1934
      Pro N, Ph-2: Mrs. L. M. Pullia; Expenditures for Nursing, 1915-1934; July 9, 1936
      Pro N, Ph-3: Mary Beard; Nursing Needs; September 29, 1937
    - Program and Policy - Nursing, Public Health - Reports - Pro N, Ph-4 - Pro N, Ph-6, 1942-1950 (Box 15, Folder 166)
      Pro N, Ph-4: Mary E. Tennant; Summary of the Nursing Program, Statement Prepared for Scientific Directors (incorporated in Review of Program Presented at Scientific Directors Meeting, September 11, 1942. Complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
      Pro N, Ph-5: Mary E. Tennant; International Health Division Nursing Objectives and Methods Employed for Their Advancement, Presented at International Health Division Staff Meeting; May 19, 1948
      Pro N, Ph-6: Mary E. Tennant; Resume of Rockefeller Foundation Public Health Nursing and Nursing Education Activities (complete reports filed RG 3.1 908 Pro CR-3); July 6, 1950
    - Program and Policy - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Program and Policy - Nutrition, 1941-1948 (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - Program and Policy - Nutrition - Report - Pro Nut-1, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 169)
      Pro Nut-1: Nutrition, Extract from review of program presented to the Scientific Directors September 11, 1942 (complete report field RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Public Health Education, 1913-1951 (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Program and Policy - Public Health Education, 1913-1951 (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - Program and Policy - Public Health Education - Report - Pro PHE-1, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 172)
      Pro PHE-1: John A. Ferrell; Public Health Personnel in United States Training Facilities; Needs for Future Suggested Programs; September 26, 1938
    - Program and Policy - Public Health Education - Report - Pro PHE-2, 1942, Tables 1953 (Box 15, Folder 173)
      Pro PHE-2: Public Health Education; 1942
      Tables: Public Health Education, Rockefeller Foundation Expenditures, Record of Public Health Schools, IHD Fellowships; 1917-1949
    - Program and Policy - Public Health Laboratories, 1917-1926 (Box 15, Folder 174)
    - Program and Policy - Rabies (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - Program and Policy - Rabies - Report - Pro RAB-1, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 176)
      Pro RAB-1: Rabies, Extract from Review of Program Presented to Scientific Directors (Complete Report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Reports (Unpublished) - Correspondence, 1929-1960 (Box 16, Folder 177)
    - Program and Policy - Reports (Unpublished) - Correspondence, 1929-1960 (Box 16, Folder 178)
    - Program and Policy - Report, 1953-1970 (list) (Box 16, Folder 179)
      International Health Division and Division of Medicine and Public Health, Report File, List of Contents in Outside Storage; June 1953- November 1960
    - Program and Policy - Respiratory Diseases, 1918-1950 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - Program and Policy - Respiratory Diseases, 1918-1950 (Box 16, Folder 181)
    - Program and Policy - Respiratory Diseases - Report - Pro RES-1, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 182)
      Pro RES-1: Respiratory Diseases, Extract from Review of Program presented to Scientific Directors (Complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Soil-Born Diseases, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - Program and Policy - Soil-Born Diseases - Report - Pro SOI-1, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 184)
      Pro SOH-1: Control of Soil-Borne Diseases, Extract from Review of Program presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Statistical Analysis - Cross Reference (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - Program and Policy - Statistical Analysis - Report - Pro STAT-1, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 186)
      Pro SOH-1: Supplementary Studies, Statistical Analysis, Extract from Review of Program presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Syphilis - Cross Reference (Box 16, Folder 187)
    - Program and Policy - Syphilis - Report - Pro SYP-1, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 188)
      Pro CYP-1: Syphilis, Extract from Review of Program presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Tuberculosis - Cross Reference (Box 16, Folder 189)
    - Program and Policy - Tuberculosis - Report - Pro TBC-1, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 190)
      Pro TBC-1: Tuberculosis, Extract from Review of Program presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Typhus Fever - Cross Reference (Box 16, Folder 191)
    - Program and Policy - Typhus Fever - Report - Pro TYP-1, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 192)
      Pro TYP-1: Typhus Fever, Extract from Review of Program presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
    - Program and Policy - Yellow Fever - Cross Reference (Box 16, Folder 193)
    - Program and Policy - Yellow Fever - Reports - Pro YEL-1 - Pro YEL-2, 1942-1948 (Box 16, Folder 194)
      Pro YEL-1: Yellow Fever, Extract from Review of Program presented to Scientific Directors (complete report filed RG 3.1 908 Pro-24); September 11, 1942
      Pro YEL-2: Andrew J. Warren; Yellow Fever; December 2, 1948
    - Scientific Directors - Minutes, 1944-1949 (Box 16, Folder 0194a)
    - Scientific Directors, 1928-1941 (Box 16, Folder 195)
    - Scientific Directors, 1942-1944 (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - Scientific Directors, 1945-1954 (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - Staff, 1915-1937 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - Staff, 1928-1941 (Box 17, Folder 199)
    - Staff, 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 200)
    - Staff, 1946-1956 (Box 17, Folder 201)
    - Staff - Reports - Staff-2, 2a, 2b, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 202)
      Staff-2: International Health Commission/Board/Division/Staff Members, Data from Minutes Compiled by Pauline Mead; 1913-1927
      Staff-2a: Pauline A. Mead; International Health Commission/Board/Division, Staff Members (alphabetic list); 1913-1947
      Staff-2b: International Health Commission/Board/Division; Staff Members who have served more than Three Years; 1913-1948
  - Insurance, Medical Care, Personnel, 1914-1949; 909; 1 document case
    Correspondence, memoranda, reports, and directives concerning personnel policies, practices, and benefits. Included are copies of insurance policies and directories of the New York staff, 1950-1974. Also included is a file documenting participation by the New York office staff in the Foster Parents program which contains their correspondence with two "adopted" children.
    - Insurance - Accident, 1926, 1931, 1935-1936, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Insurance - Malpractice, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Insurance - Personnel - Paris Office, 1928, 1932, 1934-1936, 1940, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Insurance - Policies, 1919, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Insurance - Property, 1926, 1928-1929, 1933-1934, 1937-1942, 1945-1947, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Insurance - Unemployment and Disability, 1935, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Insurance - Workman's Compensation, 1919, 1928, 1932-1933, 1937-1942, 1945-1947, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Personnel - General, 1914, 1916, 1923, 1929-1936, 1939-1943, 1945-1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Personnel - Freight, 1929, 1934, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Personnel - Furniture Loss, 1928-1930, 1934, 1937-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Personnel - Holidays, 1916, 1928, 1937-1942, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Personnel - Military Service, 1917-1918, 1939-1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Personnel - Policy and Practice - Report of January 4, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Personnel - Salaries, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Social Sciences, 1914-1978; 910; 11 document cases
    Correspondence, memoranda, and reports concerning program and policy decisions related to the evolution and development of a program in the social sciences. Economics, international relations, psychology, housing, public administration, and aging research are some of the topics covered.
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Program and Policy, 1928-1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-1 - Pro-4, 1914-1927 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Pro-1 DR 22: Memorandum re: Institute for Social and Economic Research (Proposed); January 21, 1914
      Pro-2 DR 33: Majority and Minority Report of Committee on the Institute for Social and Economic Research (Proposed); August 4, 1914
      Pro-3: Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Policy, Extracts for Various Memoranda and Dockets; 1922-1926
      Pro-4: Social Technology- Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial; 1927
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-5, 5a, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Pro 5 DR 382: Principles of Governing Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Policy in Social Science, Presented at Rockefeller Foundation Meeting; December 31, 1928
      Pro-5a: Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Appropriations; April 30, 1928
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-6 - Pro-12, Pro 12a, 1929-1933 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Pro-6: Recent Trends in Social Sciences, Speech delivered at the Dedication of the Social Science Building at the University of Chicago Beardsley Ruml; December 17, 1929
      Pro-7: Institutions in the United States Eligible for Grants for General Social Science research; January 28, 1930
      Pro-8: Sydnor H. Walker; Schools of Social Work; February 1931
      Pro-9: Summary of Appropriations, Pledges, Authorizations and Estimates with Probable Year of Payment; June 30, 1931
      Pro-11 DR 475: Excerpt from Interim Report of Activities of the Rockefeller Foundation, Presented at the Trustees Meeting (Complete report filed 3.1 900 Pro-24); December 13, 1933
      Pro-12: Edmund E. Day; Proposed Program with Indications of Financial Implications; August 10, 1931
      Pro-12a: Edmund E. Day; Proposed Rockefeller Foundation Program in Economic Stabilization; September 14, 1931
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-13, 13a, 14, 14a, 15, 16, 17, 18, 22, 1933-1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Pro-13 DR 469: Past Program and Proposed Future Program, Extract from the Agenda for Special Trustees Meeting (Complete report including all divisions filed in 3.1 900 Pro-23); April 11, 1933
      Pro-13a DR 469: Edmund E. Day; Proposed Social Science Program of the Rockefeller Foundation (working papers used in preparation of agenda for special Rockefeller Foundation meeting, April 11, 1933); March 13, 1933
      Pro-14: Interim Report of Activities During 1933 in Fields of Concentration, Proposed at April 11, 1933 Meeting; December 13, 1933
      Pro-14a: Beardsley Ruml; Memorandum regarding Objectives; December 1933
      Pro-15 DR 468: Extract from the Report of the Committee on Appraisal and Planning Presented at the Trustees Meeting (Complete report filed 900 Pro-27); December 11, 1934
      Pro-16: Social Sciences Staff Conference, Review of Program and Staff Assignments; December 18, 1934
      Pro-17: Surveys made in Connection with Review of Program; March 1935
      Pro-18 DR 492: New Program in the Social Sciences, Trustees Meeting (Excerpts filed 910 Pro Pub-3, Pro Crim-1, Pro Eco-1, Pro Hous-4, Pro Int-3); April 10, 1935
      Pro-22: Social Sciences- Extract from Statement of Program Presented at Special Trustees Conference (complete report filed 900 Pro-30, Working Papers filed 910 Pro-22a); December 15, 1936
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-19 - 21, 22a, 23, 24, 1929-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Pro-19: Social Science Appropriations Current November 1935, Classified as to Probable Disposition (with Estimated of Appropriations Required to Complete Liquidation of Old Program); November 1935
      Pro-20: Memorandum on Social Science Statement regarding Budget for 1936; November 22, 1935
      Pro-21 DR 500: The Social Science Budget, Extract from the Director's Report on Program Trustees Meeting (Complete report filed 900 Pro-28); December 11, 1935
      Pro-22a: The Social Science Program and Budget for 1936, Working papers for the Social Science section of 910 Pro-22; 1936
      Pro-23: Sydnor H. Walker, John V. VanSickle, Stacy May; Reports of Program Prepared for Meeting of Trustees Advisory Committee (Individual sections filed 910 Pro Int-4, 910 Pro Eco-1, 910 Pro Pub-5. Complete copy filed 910 Pro Ter-2); March 1938
      Pro-24: Social Sciences, Appropriations Classified; 1929-1938
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-24a, b, c, 1929-1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Pro-24a: Appropriations for Social Sciences; January 1, 1929 - December 31, 1937
      Pro-24b: Summary of Appropriations with Probable Year of Payment; April 15, 1939
      Pro-24c: Summary of Appropriations, Pledges and Authorizations with Probable Year of Payment; 1940
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-25 - Pro-30, 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Pro-25: Robert T. Crane (Social Science Research Council); Memorandum, Discussion of Social Sciences Program and Suggestions for Future Development; October 27, 1938
      Pro-26 DR 538: Dodds, Dulles and Stewart (Rockefeller Brothers Fund); Report of the Trustee Committee on Social Sciences, Presented at the Board Meeting; December 7, 1938
      Pro-27: JWP and JHW; Summary Statement, Development of the Social Science Program; January 30, 1939
      Pro-28: Tracy B. Kitterage; European Programs of Study Related to International Problems (Copies filed 910 Pro Int-5); July 19, 1940
      Pro-29: Joseph Willits; Foundation and Economic Research; January 1941
      Pro-30: Social Sciences, Notes on Europe (following trip by JHW); 1939
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-31 - Pro-35, 1939-1943 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Pro-31: Robert Redfield; Functions of Social Sciences; April 1942
      Pro-32: Chester I. Barnard; Memorandum on the Nature of the Social Sciences; April 1942
      Pro-33: Analysis of Program in Relation to Changing World Conditions Preliminary Divisional Statement used at Officer's Conference (Complete Report filed 900 Pro-35); October 7, 1942
      Pro-34: Letters of Robert Warren; December 8, 1939-1943
      Pro-35: Joseph Willits; The Social Sciences in 1944, Analysis; October 20, 1943
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-36, 37, 37a, 38, 38a, 1939-1950 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Pro-36: Social Sciences excerpt from Plans for Future Work of the Rockefeller Foundation, used as a basis for discussion at Trustees Meeting April 4, 1945 (Complete report filed 900 Pro-44. See also 900 Pro-40a); 1944
      Pro-37: Joseph Willits and other Social Science Officers; Memorandum, Future Program in the Light of Reduced Budget; 1948-1949
      Pro-37a: Joseph H. Willits and other Social Sciences Officers; Summary of Memorandum on Future Programs in the Light of Reduced Budget; 1948-1949
      Pro-38: Appropriation Daa, Social Science Program; 1939-1949
      Pro-38a: Joseph H. Willits; The Program in the Social Sciences, Excerpt from Trustees' Confidential Report (Rewrite of RG 3.1 910 Pro-38); June 1, 1950
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-39 - Pro-43, 1946-1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Pro-39: Joseph H. Willits; Social Sciences and Social Studies; April 25, 1952
      Pro-40: Carl I. Hovland; Report; May 13, 1946
      Pro-41: Norman S. Buchanan; Notes on Rockefeller Foundation Program in the Social Sciences; August 1955
      Pro-42: Leland C. DeVinney; Rockefeller Foundation Program in the Social Sciences; November 22, 1961
      Pro-43: Leland C. DeVinney; The Rockefeller Foundation's Work in the Field of the Social Sciences; July 11, 1962
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-44, 1922-1948 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Pro-44: Julia M. H. Carson; The Social Sciences Before WWII (Bound with the Social Sciences Through the War and the Post-War Period 1939-1948); 1922-1939
      Julia M. H. Carson; The Social Sciences Through the War and the Post-War Period (Bound with The Social Sciences Before WWII 1922-1939); 1939-1948
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-45, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Pro-45: Edmund E. Day; Commencement Address, University of Vermont; June 15, 1931
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-46, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 0021a)
      Pro-46: Kenneth W. Thompson; Rockefeller Foundation Program in Humanities and Social Sciences; July 16, 1962
    - Program and Policy - Aging Research, 1949-1955 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Program and Policy - Agricultural Economics, 1955-1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Program and Policy - Agricultural Economics - Report - Pro Ae-1, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Pro Ae-1: Montague Yudelman; Agricultural Economics Problems; August 1956
    - Program and Policy - Anthropology Cultural, 1931-1956 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Program and Policy - Appraisal Committee - Social Research Council, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Program and Policy - Appraisal Committee - Social Research Council - Reports, 1935, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 27)